Everyone had understood what had happened -
- And then they saw me when I was relieved, so everyone in the whole hall started laughing.
It was so embarrassing!
People still remember me today on the union.
"It's you!"
Nice that everyone feels ready with their plug.
- Is this one on?
- Do I have a look in my nose?
- No, do I have?
- Yes a little.
You have...
Have I?!
Oh my God!
Sit down!
Welcome to the premiere of them calls us students!
"I live in Gothenburg. Plug in Örebro, it probably won't happen. I won't come in."
Thursday before everything starts: "Hello! You have come in via late registration for the program in Örebro.
- How fun!
- Well, and when do I start?
"On Monday."
So that...
- * Laughter * - so ...
I was very annoying, I know.
I would jump on the medical program and book my life for 5½ years, as well.
So it was a bit like this: "But God, what have I given up on?"
And how will this be?
At the same time, it was very cool too, because for the first time you would jump on an education -
- That would lead to what you wanted to be the rest of your life.
So I call my mom in the evening.
"I think I'll move to Örebro."
"Okay, where is Örebro?"
"I'll google, wait a bit!"
I have zero sense of geography, so I'm starting to google.
- "Yes, but it's easy to get there!"
- "Yeah. Where are you going to live?"
Yes, that's the next good question too ...
I took a sabbatical to be able to digest everything and recover from high school.
- It's pretty ... especially if you go in for grades - yes, of course.
I didn't invest so much on the college exam.
You can get in through that too.
And then it became that you ...
I didn't feel ready to get into the studies again.
- No, I understand.
I needed to get some other kind of experience.
So I worked at McDonald's and turned burgers.
I got very comfortable in the hall.
I knew I was going to study, because I just come from high school.
- Yes exactly.
- I took the student this summer, and I already knew -
- That I wanted to continue because I want to be finished earlier, later.
I had been here the year before and checked in, because I saw Örebro as a suitable candidate.
It was close, but I still wanted to test my wings and move to a new city.
- But still not too far from the parents.
- No, of course.
It was the first time.
I had lived at home for 19 years before moving here.
So it was a big step to start living yourself.
Have your own accommodation, wash, cook.
I remember how I stood at home and practiced frying mom Scan's meatballs to be ready.
For the introduction I could catch up.
I just felt that: My God, I've lived for a long time now.
I still haven't gone up in rank from sausage stroganoff.
I'm still there.
- I understand.
- the best I know is when you don't have to cook -
- And you can eat roasted sandwiches for dinner.
- Yes, but I also know it.
My favorite food is just sandwiches.
It's so simple, it's just buying bread, butter and optional toppings
- It's kind of better than anything.
- I know!
Prio one is to pass the studies.
After all, that is the reason why you are in the city and plug in at Örebro University.
- It's for the sake of studies.
- Yes.
But to cope with e.g.
The MSc Program which is four years old -
It had been 10 minutes.
You have a routine that you feel the pocket if the phone is there.
And so I feel that, shit, I don't have my phone on me.
- Okay, my bank card ... I'll shop afterwards.
- You should live.
I want to be able to come home.
Shit, I put it in the toilet.
- So I just get up.
I sat in the middle of an auditorium.
- You just stand up?
Yes, in panic I get up very fast.
Everyone looks at me and wonders what's going on.
The lecturer also looks at me and wonders what is happening.
Does anyone have died, kind of?
I'm just running out.
"Excuse me, excuse, let go of me!"
Goes from the middle towards the edge and out of the hall.
The toilet was free, so when I get to it I see that nothing is there.